Ever wondered what actually works when
it comes to coding agents? Hi, [music]
my name is Maria Gorinova and I am an AI
researcher here at Tessle. I'll be
giving a webinar together with our head
of [music] product and design, Drew Nox,
on the 19th of March at 4 p.m. UK time.
With traditional software, [music] you
can run tests, you can run static
analysis, but when it comes to agents,
things are entirely different. The skill
that you just wrote might work well for
one example and then completely fail the
next one. [music] Agents require a
different way of thinking. In this
session, we will walk through designing
tests for your skills that give you real
insights. What evaluation criteria
should you use? How do you assess if
your changes will work reliably? And how
do you use all of these [music] to
continuously improve your agents
performance? If you're an engineer,
[music] a researcher or a technical
leader building with agents and you want
to make decisions clouded in data, this
one is for you. It's free to [music]
attend. Follow the link to register. We
hope to see you there.